Narrator: 10
Speaker 1: arrive
Speaker 2: leave
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: break
Speaker 2: mend
repair
Narrator: 4
Speaker 1: buy
Speaker 2: sell
Narrator: 15
Speaker 1: download
Speaker 2: upload
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: find
Speaker 2: lose
Narrator: 7
Speaker 1: forget
Speaker 2: remember
Narrator: 2
Speaker 1: lend
Speaker 2: borrow
Narrator: 16
Speaker 1: love
Speaker 2: hate
Narrator: 14
Speaker 1: miss
Speaker 2: catch
Narrator: 8
Speaker 1: pass
Speaker 2: fail
Narrator: 17
Speaker 1: pick up
Speaker 2: drop off
Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: push
Speaker 2: pull
Narrator: 12
Speaker 1: send
Speaker 2: get
receive
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: start
Speaker 2: finish
stop
Narrator: 11
Speaker 1: teach
Speaker 2: learn
Narrator: 9
Speaker 1: turn on
Speaker 2: turn off
Narrator: 13
Speaker 1: win
Speaker 2: lose